bentley.edu 2011-11-25

# Bentley University Information Privacy Statement | Bentley University

### Scope:

Bentley exercises care and prudence in the handling of personal information collected via [www.bentley.edu](http://www.bentley.edu/) and its various sub-domains, and conducts its business in ways that demonstrate respect for personal privacy. This privacy statement applies to the [www.bentley.edu](http://www.bentley.edu/) domain, and administrative applications used for e-commerce linked to [www.bentley.edu](http://www.bentley.edu/), and not to internal and/or external web sites that might be linked to or from it. Bentley’s web sites may contain links to other web sites. Bentley is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those other web sites. We reserve the right to revise our privacy policy as changing circumstances and evolving technology standards require. Such changes will be posted to this site.

### Our Information Collection Practices:

Personal information about you is not gathered when you visit the Bentley University web site unless you choose to supply information to us.

Bentley makes use of conventional online data entry forms to collect personal information from web visitors who choose to identify themselves for purposes of transacting e-commerce or receiving products, services or information.

Department web sites that collect data of any type are required to abide by, and provide a link to, Bentley's information privacy statement. We request no more information than is required to fulfill the purpose for which the information is being collected.

We support Bentley-hosted applications that collect data for e-commerce purposes. We also maintain partnerships with selected vendors to process e-commerce transactions on our behalf. These e-commerce transactions are secured with SSL and maintain high standards of privacy, to which approved sub-contracting vendors are also held.

Bentley's web site neither targets persons who are less than 13 years of age nor knowingly collects personal information online from them.

Bentley contracts with the NACElink Network to provide students with résumé services, job listings, and an on-campus recruiting and advising system. As part of this service, students and registered alumni can post resumes. Students can also schedule appointments, apply for jobs, and schedule on-campus interviews. The information in a candidate’s profile resides on the NaceLink network and is used by Bentley for advising, promoting programs and services, notifying candidates of employment opportunities, and referring qualified candidates to employers. Jobs posted to the NaceLink Network are not screened by NACE. Please refer to the NACElink Privacy Statement for technical details and a description of the NACElink.com site.

### How We Use Cookies:

Cookies are small text files that web sites (like [www.bentley.edu](http://www.bentley.edu/)) use to store small amounts of information.

Cookies do not record your name or other personally identifiable information; nor can they be used to control your computer, to access your other files, or to reveal other sites you visit online.

### Bentley and our third-party vendors use cookies:

  * to help Bentley add features and functionality to our site, e.g., to verify default variables and to enable single-sign-on for other Bentley applications.
  * to collect anonymous visitor data in order to generate aggregated statistics that help us understand how visitors use our site. Statistics include the volume, variety, timing and other characteristics of our web traffic.

### How We Use Your Information:

We use the information you submit to provide you with the product or service you requested, consistent with the purpose for which the information was collected.

We may on occasion disclose statistical information to third parties in an aggregate, anonymous form.

At present, Bentley does not make alternate uses of information collected through e-commerce transactions. But in the future, we may elect to send you information about the institution, its programs and events.

We do not share, trade, or sell personal information to third parties without your consent except

  * in limited ways as required by law, and
  * with sub-contractors engaged by us to provide services, and
  * for purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

We do not combine web traffic analysis information with personal information such as name, age, phone number and mailing address.

### Important Technical Information:

Bentley follows industry-standard precautions and procedures in the transmission and storage of electronic data. When you make online payments, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) server software in conjunction with your SSL-enabled-browser software prevents unauthorized access to the information you submit by encrypting it during transmission. While we remain committed to protecting the privacy of our users, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. We do so by using secure technology, privacy protection controls, and restrictions on employee access.

### Accuracy of Information:

All information provided on the official Bentley web site is for informational purposes only and does not constitute a legal contract between the institution and any other person or entity otherwise specified.

Although every reasonable effort is made to present current and accurate information and to monitor web content for compliance with institutional policy, Bentley makes no guarantees of any kind, nor does it take institutional responsibility for undetected, noncompliant conditions created without its knowledge or consent and in violation of its policy.

Information on [www.bentley.edu](http://www.bentley.edu/) is subject to change without prior notice.

### Your Choices:

You are not required to provide personal information to visit our web site.

Some (but not all) of Bentley's third-party vendors allow visitors to opt-out from using that vendor's cookies.

If you choose to provide personal information such as your e-mail address, mailing address or phone number, Bentley may contact you.

If you receive unwanted contacts and wish to be excluded from future such contacts, please inform us at the e-mail address below, specifying the source and providing a description of the unwanted materials. We will notify the appropriate office accordingly.

If you see a photo of yourself on [www.bentley.edu](http://www.bentley.edu/) which you would like removed, please contact [marketing@bentley.edu](mailto:marketing@bentley.edu).

Bentley encourages you to take advantage of settings within web browsers to disable all or certain cookies and to utilize other tools that enhance user privacy on the Internet.

In the course of doing business, Bentley performs numerous administrative functions and services via its web site and reserves the right to require participation in them by students and staff.

For additional information on Bentley's privacy information practices, including our data classification policies, please visit the information privacy web site.

#### Effective Date: July 25, 2007

How to Contact Us: [infoprivacy@bentley.edu](mailto:infoprivacy@bentley.edu).
